Bluetooth My name is Rajesh Mangilal Jain
in my shop chamber after one hour in the
name of PIMS and I have just a few days
ago taken a policy in the name of President and opening
whose name is Rajya and a few days ago
I had taken policy
E A Nice from ICICI Lombard by confirming it for this reason as if there was a
theft in the shop
then we took a policy from that shop for a while and
suddenly while roaming around it all got deleted then I
remember that I have returned then at my
home itself Uncle ji all from your life insurance
so he told me that this is how to do it,
gradually I submitted the papers, I got support from the
company as well as from the license
side and now right now we have also got a
clear settlement of lakhs of rupees,
now we are happy, we also
say thanks to this mixture, we praise such faces
and tell everyone that work from your section,
I am from Ujjain and completely from here